I know that may﻿ sound stupid, but...
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a bipedal tank.
>Investigate?
>>Yes.
>No.
>While investigating it, you ended up in some lost island near Alaska in a archipelago.
AvengerofWarcraft hace 20 horas
Welcome back.
Yes. I like﻿ this song.
*sits down with Nanako for a tea party...like a boss*
EstelleTheHedgehog hace 1 día en la lista de reproducción Persona 4 Soundtrack
>You open the fridge
>It's Igor's nose
>Eat﻿ it?
>Yes
>Your Understanding has increased!
TheSlammurai hace 4 días 3  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
i REALLY want Persona 4 on PSN ﻿
ultimatenarutofan100 hace 1 semana en la lista de reproducción Favorite videos
Nice song. Thanks﻿ for the link.
thedarKnight2008 hace 3 semanas
~MISHEARD LYRICS~
Sounds of glove oh the oudouceba treeeeeees
Baby, don't go lick us-- waaaaaaiiiiit, I﻿ know
All this time =, running and eating liiiiight
Pleeeeeeaaaassse, pass twooooooooooo
Burrit0burger hace 4 semanas en la lista de reproducción Shin Megami Tensei: Persona 4
I'll﻿ be damned if it wasn't right for a mis-trans. XD
KiyonoHime en respuesta a Burrit0burger (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 semana
[You watched the Midnight Channel while eating Nanako's﻿ Science project.]
Burrit0burger hace 4 semanas en la lista de reproducción Shin Megami Tensei: Persona 4 3  
With the ultimate poker﻿ face. XD
KiyonoHime en respuesta a Burrit0burger (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 semana
Your stomach realizes what you're trying to do and﻿ rebels. You stop trying to eat the grass.
xSesuKunx hace 1 mes
>You open the fridge.
>There's some wasabi in the fridge.
>....Lick it?
>>[Yes] No
>You licked the wasabi.
>It was a terrible decision, the tears won't stop flowing from your﻿ eyes.
>Your courage has increased.
blackblur589 hace 1 mes 11  
@00:40
"Should we give a﻿ shit?"
jackal912 hace 1 mes 2  
It's "Should we give it﻿ shot?"
wind430 en respuesta a jackal912 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes en la lista de reproducción More videos from Slayer0
Thats what i thought﻿ LOL
JoeysaurousRex en respuesta a jackal912 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes en la lista de reproducción Liked videos
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
every time look﻿ at the picture in the flame
Urmean15 hace 1 mes
I commend you for the excellent quality.﻿
SparklinWaterInc hace 1 mes
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
KamuiKunitsuna hace 1 mes
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Who opens the refrigerator more﻿ often after looking at these comments?
Toonzsedaki hace 1 mes
>You open the fridge.
>You see Adachi inside.
>You close the door to the fridge upon his insistence.
>You ponder how he got inside﻿ your fridge in the first place.
>Your expression has significantly increased!
TheUncannyX hace 1 mes
> Nanako "Welcome Home Big... *pass out*
> Should You Help Nanako
>> [Yes] No Call Dojima
> You Don't have enough Understanding To Save Nanako , Game﻿ Over
XxTylerTheDragonXx hace 1 mes 3  
>You open the fridge
>There's some cabbage. Adachi brought it yesterday. It looks kinda weird.
>Eat it?
>Yes
>You eated the cabbage
>You don't know why, but you﻿ see women as bitches and whores.
TheChosedOne7 hace 2 meses 8  
>The next day,you saw yourself inside the TV﻿
Adachi Tohru en respuesta a TheChosedOne7 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes
"Eated" the cabbage?﻿
JonnyLikesGames87 en respuesta a TheChosedOne7 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes
>You open the fridge
>You saw lots﻿ of fridge jokes
>Make one?
>Yes
>You're actually making one now
Adachi Tohru hace 2 meses 5  
FRIDGE BRILLIANCE!!!
And you made﻿ another.
Shinogu en respuesta a Adachi Tohru (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes
"Well come back Big bro!"﻿
mine turtle hace 2 meses
Stop opening the fridge, you are gonna break﻿ the door.
tenryuzora hace 2 meses 8  
>You open the fridge.
>It's empty.
>You realize the fridge is a metaphor for your﻿ life.
>You smack Nanako around a little bit to let out all your pent up passive aggression.
KirkJohnson34 hace 2 meses 7  
>You open the fridge.
>Put on your glasses?
>>[Yes] No
>You decide that these﻿ fridge jokes are too mainstream and go to bed.
IcyPheonix3 hace 2 meses 15  
With glasses?﻿
tenryuzora en respuesta a IcyPheonix3 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 meses
>You open the fridge
>There's a funny series of youtube comments inside.
>Join in?
>>[Yes]﻿ No
>You decided to comment with it.
>Nothing has changed.
maychanx31 hace 2 meses 7  
Oh god, those weird noises ARE in the song! For some reason, I thought the game﻿ was glitching out on me for some time, like something with the menus.
VGKing hace 2 meses en la lista de reproducción Shin Megami Tensei: Persona 4
...?﻿
betrekwoman en respuesta a VGKing (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 meses
>You open the fridge
>There's a bandwagon﻿ inside
>Jump on it?
Thomas Bisset hace 2 meses 83  
YES.﻿
KiyonoHime en respuesta a Thomas Bisset (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 semana
every day's great at your junes.﻿
Runeless hace 2 meses
That slice of ham... I﻿ feel a disturbance in the force...
DeathLisk hace 2 meses 3  
>You open the fridge.
>A voice from inside informs you that there is no Dana, only Zuul.
>You close﻿ the fridge, while pondering who you can call about this.
Mageboobs hace 2 meses 10  
>You open the fridge.
>Nothing catches your eye.
>Eat nothing?
>>Yes
>You ate nothing. You don't feel any different.
>What did you think was going to happen?
>You﻿ went to bed, full up on the nothing.
VaatiOfDarkness hace 2 meses 2  
>You open the fridge.
>A baby is inside.
>Eat it...?
>>Yes
>Hariti appears and tells you to eat﻿ the pomegranate instead.
>You eat it, but you wonder why there was a baby inside the fridge.
>You shrug and go to bed...
VaatiOfDarkness hace 2 meses 2  
>You opened the fridge.
>You found a ciggerate lighter.
>Take it and randomly flip it out during cutscenes?
>>Yes
>You took it and flip it out.
>Fans﻿ now consider you a 'Tatsuya Suou' rip off.
VaatiOfDarkness hace 2 meses 2  
Where﻿ have you been?...whoops, wrong game:)
Hlben10 hace 2 meses
WELCOME﻿ BACK!
detroitsbest hace 2 meses en la lista de reproducción Persona4 OST
sheesh in the middle of this, I got up and went to the kitchen...couldn't find anything I am starving for even though I'm starving...I think I'm going to play some Persona now.﻿
Temayuka hace 3 meses
I really like all the music﻿ in this game
abdnumber4 hace 3 meses 2  
Onri time monday, see that﻿ light? Geez, has too...
PocketGodEnthusiast hace 3 meses
Sounds﻿ of lore Oh douch a deuce my dreams, baby Domo link a... Swim, oh.
PocketGodEnthusiast hace 3 meses
>You open﻿ the fridge
>There's a hamburger inside
>Ice Break?
Growlzagra hace 3 meses
>Implying I﻿ opened the fridge.
ismail guendouli hace 3 meses 3  
I didn't first like this song but now when I'm alone﻿ I miss this
nesfan8 hace 3 meses
This song has an awesome﻿ bassline.
skystarless hace 3 meses 3  
>You opened the fridge.
>Nothing catches your eye...
WELL OBVIOUSLY PERSONA 4, YOU DON'T KNOW HOW HUNGRY I AM. D8﻿
KingdomHeartsGirl000 hace 4 meses 5  
=')﻿
xLunaOscurax hace 4 meses en la lista de reproducción Persona 4 ♪ ♫
0:39﻿ - So i give a shit...
hannahjonas182 hace 4 meses
I could've sworn I heard something in the lyrics...
"That your﻿ dick so haaaard"
THE HELL?!!??!
machinimamarlon hace 4 meses
>you opened the fridge
>you see some bread lying in a corner
>burn it?﻿ [YES] YES
>I WILL BURN MY BREEEEAAAD!!
MultiFinalfantasy7 hace 4 meses 63  
Gonna﻿ Burn yo Bread.
thegreat6thhokage en respuesta a MultiFinalfantasy7 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 14 horas
>You opened﻿ the fridge.
>You see an apple inside.
>Bring it to your room?
[Yes] No
>Ryuk enjoyed your lunch!
TitanioVerde hace 4 meses 6  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
MultiFinalfantasy7 hace 4 meses
i was surprised when i came home from﻿ school and my mom accidentally played this song.
sweetbuble90210 hace 4 meses en la lista de reproducción Shin Megami Tensei: Persona 4
I thought for sure the lyrics to this song would be one of the﻿ top comments.
DragoSonicMile hace 4 meses
"You have enough ingredence to make Daigaku﻿ Imo"
"What do you mean you don't know what that is, OFCOURESE YOU DO!"
DakkoX hace 4 meses 4  
>You open the fridge.
>You see some pickles stored inside of a tuppleware container.
>Eat it?
>>[Yes] No
>...
>That was the worst thing you could've done.
>Those were actually old hot dog links.
>You decided to﻿ go to bed early.
GreentheGunstar hace 4 meses 3  
>You open the﻿ fridge
>You see a bunch of "you open the fridge" jokes
>Eat them?
Growlzagra hace 4 meses 4  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the fridge
>You see a tape in it
>Take it to your room to play on the VCR tape recorder? [yes] no
~~~~~
>You play the tape...
>... You hear the mysterious sounds of a man running away from something...
>... You hear static
>You feel like your being watched by prying eyes from within the T.V
>"This is the end for you..."
>You can now﻿ explore the end! Who knows what dangers are in store for you?
leishify hace 4 meses
I get it! XD﻿
Toonzsedaki en respuesta a leishify (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes
>You open the fridge.
>There's a One Eyed Laser Disco Ball inside
>Eat it?
>>YES
>Ameno-sagiri: Mankind's desires are my desires.
>You can now﻿ use the Fog of Confusion!
ncala hace 4 meses 6  
Every time I eat something unusual out of﻿ the fridge, I get 40% more manly.
TheRipperPrince hace 4 meses
>You open the fridge.
>There's a potato chip inside.
>Eat it?
>>[Yes] No
>You decided to take a potato chip... AND EAT IT!
>Your Expression has significantly﻿ increased!
866marluxia hace 4 meses 147  
hahaha so Death Note real XD﻿
CloudStrife0896 en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
One of the best posts I've seen on the net. Kudos!﻿
pastelshrimp en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 3 meses
You﻿ sir are epic.
Sisthra en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 3 meses
Still can't figure﻿ out how that worked. lol
kriger619 en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 3 meses
Death﻿ Note reference xD
Music1uv3r279 en respuesta a kriger619 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 meses
Congratulations, you are the﻿ new king of the internet
TeamDeltaMAXXX en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 meses
>You open the fridge
>There's a large laptop inside
>go inside? [Yes] Yes
>you have finally landed the internet server,now throw people﻿ in
Adachi Tohru en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 meses 3  
DAT DEATH NOTE REFERANCE!﻿
silv3rs0ul98 en respuesta a 866marluxia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 mes
I AM FAVOURITING THIS JUST FOR﻿ THE FRIDGE JOKES XDDD
chelseafcrocks82 hace 5 meses
C-C-COMBO BREAKER!﻿
SparklinWaterInc hace 5 meses
Thou art I...And I am thou...
Thou hast established a new bond...
It brings thee closer to the truth...
Thou﻿ shalt be blessed when creating
Personas of the Hermit Arcana...
> You have established the Expired Food Social Link of the Hermit Arcana!
<8(...The food can not only talk, but it's developing FEELINGS for me now!?
GreentheGunstar hace 5 meses 6  
*Everytime I get back home, with Nanako's Social Link available*
:D NANAKO! Let's watch Featherman R!!! YAAAAY!!!
*Every time﻿ I get back home, with Ryotaro's Social Link available*
:D Uncle! Let's drink all the expired milk in the fridge! We're goin' for the Gallon Challenge! >8D You better STEP IT UP MOTHERFU--
*Coming back home everyday during November*
<:(...<:,(...Nanako...Uncle...­Where are you?
GreentheGunstar hace 5 meses 3  
*FOREVER﻿ ALONE...*
AverruncusFate en respuesta a GreentheGunstar (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
> You opened the fridge
> It seems you have enough ingredients to make an omelette, Province style, for dinner.
> Will you make an omelette? (*YES*/NO)
> You wanted to make an omelette, but you don't have enough Diligence.
> Seriously! It's at "Callow." You're lazy as﻿ f***.
<:(...I'm hungry...
GreentheGunstar hace 5 meses 5  
>You open the fridge
>You notice the lack of food in it
>You question where your﻿ dinner is coming from
>. . . You should probably go to bed
ShowFizzle hace 5 meses 7  
>You﻿ opened the fridge.
>There's a pomegranate inside.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>Hariti appears and casts Bufudyne on you.
Life is truth, and never a dream...
VaatiOfDarkness hace 5 meses 4  
>You opened the fridge.
>There's some some yellow liquid﻿ inside.
>...Drink it?
>Yes
>...You should probably go to the hospital.
MRGabriel123856 hace 5 meses
> You open the fridge
> there is a can of green juice
> eat it?
>yes
>that wasn't green juice
>you feel as though a million teeth brushings will never get your﻿ mouth clean
nesskirby7 hace 5 meses
i like to risten to this﻿ when i dont know wtf to do in my room
Andelin09 hace 5 meses 2  
I came here for the Fridge jokes, stayed for the Signs of Love.﻿
Disgracetotheline hace 5 meses 2  
in soviet russia, fridge opens﻿ you...
jdsjkaglfkj hace 5 meses en la lista de reproducción Liked videos
>greentext everywhere
oh fuck you﻿ guys.
24oscar24 hace 5 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
Deviltriggerfounder hace 5 meses
> You opened the﻿ fridge
> Rorschach is inside
ENEMY ADVANTAGE!!
crossbones116 hace 5 meses 3  
So﻿ much win
Deviltriggerfounder en respuesta a crossbones116 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 5 meses
>You opened a Youtube window
>You realized﻿ you don't have anything to write about
>You decided not to write a comment
tintor2 hace 5 meses 3  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
TitanioVerde en respuesta a tintor2 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 5 meses
THUMBS UP 4 lilbonsly's﻿ COMMENT!!! xD
RazorWind98 hace 5 meses
>You﻿ Opened the Fridge
>You forgot why you opened the fridge
>You close the fridge
lilbonsly hace 5 meses 114  
True story, bro.﻿
AvP106 en respuesta a lilbonsly (Mostrar el comentario) hace 5 meses
You decided to﻿ watch the Midnight Channel while eating Nanako's science project.
Crok425 hace 5 meses
>You opened the cabinet.
>You see a jar of nutella.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>The﻿ plastic jar had a strange taste. In fact, you don't feel good.
>You left the Nutella alone...
bowsercrushmario hace 5 meses 6  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the comments section
>You search for hours for your comment that had top comment months ago.
> . . . After thousands of crappy fridge jokes﻿ you realize that youtube has become even dumber and accidentally removed all your old comments.
>. . . you should probably go to bed
ShowFizzle hace 5 meses
>You open the fridge
>You saw a container with﻿ King moron's puke inside it
>Eat it?
>Yes
>you felt that a million of toothbrushes and dentists wont help you get clean
MultiFinalfantasy7 hace 5 meses
>You opened the fridge
>You see a jar of a strange, yellow liquid
>Drink it?
>>Yes
>No
>You now have the urge to toss jars of yellow liquid at Frenchmen in suites.﻿
biancachan hace 5 meses 2  
> You﻿ open the fridge.
> You see a plate of burnt bread.
> Eat it?
>> Yes
*Nyx comes out*
Minato: DAMN YOU SOUJI!!!
dmoquinn hace 5 meses 5  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
Aakkosti hace 6 meses
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the fridge
>You saw Shadow Naoto (again??)
>Shadow Naoto : 'since you destroyed my secret base, this is my NEW secret﻿ base, keep it a secret will you?'
>Keep this a secret??
ValetinoLovebird hace 6 meses 7  
>YES!! DAMN YES!!﻿
IzanagiSMT en respuesta a ValetinoLovebird (Mostrar el comentario) hace 5 meses
These jokes﻿ aren't beary funny.
riku54321 hace 6 meses 10  
> You opened the fridge.
> Nanako is inside. She says:
> "Welcome﻿ to the fridge, big bro!"
> Go in?
Aakkosti hace 6 meses 11  
>no
>....
> you﻿ deiced to go to bed early after witnessing that...
MehTheBoy en respuesta a Aakkosti (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
HOLY FUCK THESE FRIDGE﻿ JOKES ARE SOOOOO FUNNY JUST KIDDING xDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD­DDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD­DDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD
cambone729 hace 6 meses
>You Opened the Fridge >There's a red can of body spray labeled "Old spice" inside. >Use it? >Yes. >You used the body spray. >Suddenly a buff Black Man crashes through the kitchen wall >"OLD SPICE BODY﻿ SPRAY IS SO POWERFUL IT CAN SNEAK INTO YO VIDEO GAMES!" >You stand there looking confused >The Man is looking at you >"POWERRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR!!!" >Your head exploded! "Life is truth and never a dream...PO-PO-PO PA PO PA-POWER!" >The Scree explodes
Natendowii hace 6 meses 12  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the fridge.
>You﻿ see a mini-fridge.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>You realized you just created fridgeception.
>You decide to go to bed early.
RenaKunai hace 6 meses 8  
>you opened the fridge
>A﻿ wild gaben appeared
>Eat him?
>Yes
>Episode 3 will never come out now.
AkimboNinjaPWN hace 6 meses 5  
>you opened the fridge
>you saw a﻿ book lying right there
>eat it?
>yes
>dumbass
MultiFinalfantasy7 hace 6 meses 3  
"You had a﻿ dream that you and Dojima were wearing luchador masks and wrestling. Your relationship with Dojima has intensified"
ಠ_ಠ
PersonaXIII hace 6 meses 11  
> you decided to never sleep again for as long as﻿ you live....
MehTheBoy en respuesta a PersonaXIII (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses 3  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
GreentheGunstar en respuesta a PersonaXIII (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
[double commenting bro]
>You open the fridge.
>You see two stripper, Panty and Stocking.
>They are dancing on﻿ your food and taking of there underwear....
> Eat them?
>>Yes
BunnyzAreHot hace 6 meses 2  
>You opened the fridge.
> There is hundred of comments trying to make﻿ a joke.
> You don't laugh.
> You don't feel well, you decided to go bed early tonight.
BunnyzAreHot hace 6 meses 11  
You open﻿ the fridge
There wasn't a joke about the fridge in the anime
You decide to close the fridge
TheBattlesOfAllTime hace 6 meses 2  
>You open the fridge
>There's a used condom inside
>Dojima gets home and looks inside the fridge with you
>Dojima smiles wryly
Dojima: What have you been﻿ doing after school?
N-nothing Your Mom >Bringing home chicks
Dojima: Hahahaha.
Nanako: What does that mean?
DrProfSlugger hace 6 meses
This song reminds me of the time I watched the midnight channel while﻿ eating Nanako's science project.
bowsercrushmario hace 6 meses 6  
wait.﻿ What??
Temayuka en respuesta a bowsercrushmario (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
Hiimdaisy comic﻿
Crok425 en respuesta a Temayuka (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
These jokes﻿ about the fridge never get old...:3
sonanhdeptrai hace 6 meses
>You opened the frigde.
>You see some pills
>Grab them?
>>Yes
>No
>You hear﻿ a voice...
GRABBIN PEELZ
>You unlocked the Persona Louis!
ThePrincessAsshole hace 6 meses 5  
Yosuke: DUDE GET OUT OF THE HOUSE ITS BEEN 3 WEEKS!!! WE ARE WORRIED ABOUT YOU!!
Me: ;﻿ -; but i love the BGM so much....
LuckyNoDice747 hace 6 meses 4  
Congratz! the﻿ comments here are on TvTropes!
Dice12K hace 6 meses 8  
ur welcome XD﻿
blakebrown115 en respuesta a Dice12K (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
> You opened the fridge
> There's half a bottle of SKYY Vodka inside
> Drink it?
>>> Yes
> Your vision becomes blurry, and you see you and﻿ dojima trying to summon personas
> You wake up in a bed full of girls with dojima by your side
> You decide to lock such memories on the deepest levels of your heart
> You have successfully made the Persona Mother Harlot
GHLFOREVER hace 6 meses
nanako﻿ *w*
gentrelane hace 6 meses
>﻿ you open the fridge
> there is bread inside
> take the bread
> yes
> you put the bread in the toaster.
> you take out the bread
> you burned the bread
hellmaker51 hace 7 meses 8  
Burrrnnnn myyyy﻿ Dreeeaaaadddd...I mean Bread....
02AllieKat en respuesta a hellmaker51 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
Why isn't there a fridge joke in the﻿ anime yet?
cubeblast hace 7 meses
>You open the fridge
>Nothing catches your eye
...
>You open the fridge
>Surely from last time you would have known that nothing catches your eye, but you're so bored you are going to repeatedly check the fridge and cupboards anyway, in hope more food will magically﻿ appear.
>... You decide to check the cupboards once more.
XSaberMeltdownX hace 7 meses 3  
Lol I do that all the time﻿ when I'm bored. XD
02AllieKat en respuesta a XSaberMeltdownX (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
>You open the fridge
>You here the words from an unfamiliar voice in your mind..
>" i used to open the fridge like﻿ you..but then i took.."
>You slammed the fridge door shut
thesonicdome hace 7 meses 118  
LOL﻿
vaanshadow en respuesta a thesonicdome (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
took what?? my little﻿ sister's project into my mouth??
ValetinoLovebird en respuesta a thesonicdome (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge.
>you see a black cat inside
>will you eat it?
>>yes
>no
>you suddenly feel the urge to put your personas in tubes and that your side﻿ burns should be pointy
coreymantelspy7 hace 7 meses 6  
> You Open the fridge.
> There is﻿ an container with Doujimas Sperm inside.
> Drink it?
> You decided to call Kanji and tell Him about
> Emperror Arcarna Maxed.
blutundeisen hace 7 meses 4  
Dat﻿ bassline.
OmegaMetroid93 hace 7 meses
Forget the fridge, I'm going to﻿ rig something up to where it starts playing as soon as I walk through my front door :D
swat2555 hace 7 meses
>You open the fridge
>You﻿ see a box of condoms
>Take them out?
>Yes.
>Gross, they're all used!
SupprSmashBrosGirl hace 7 meses 6  
I﻿ LOVE the fridge comments! :D
TheFunGamer94 hace 7 meses
> You open the fridge.
>﻿ There is a bottle inside containing an unknown substance.
> Drink it?
> Yes.
> You drank crazy juice! YOU ARE CRAZEH!
> Crazy person is crazy.
> Hubba hubba hubba!
> You pass out...
> The next morning, at school, you are glared at by Yukiko and Chie...
> ...You decide not to ask.
TheDypo hace 7 meses 2  
>Nanako: Big bro!! I went grocery shopping today!!
>Hey, you have enough ingredients to make daigaku imo!!
>What do you mean, you don't have a clue what the heck that is? Of course you do!!
>Quick!!﻿ Pick an ingredient!! (three japanese words pops out)
AzureAlkaid hace 7 meses 2  
....well....fuck﻿
MehTheBoy en respuesta a AzureAlkaid (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
I made a mechanism so that every time I open my front door﻿ this song starts playing in the house.
seilaoque hace 7 meses 12  
Cool story, bro.﻿
DashNapalm en respuesta a seilaoque (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses 2  
cool being a dick, bro.﻿
sigurdgram en respuesta a DashNapalm (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
You HAVE to teach me how you﻿ did that.
TheK12314 en respuesta a seilaoque (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
I WANT ONE! :D﻿
longlivereligion en respuesta a seilaoque (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
> you open the﻿ fridge.
> you see nanako's dismembered body inside.
> eat it?
>> yes.
*your courage has greatly increased*
stretchyscrotum hace 7 meses
>You opened the fridge.
>There's﻿ a bag of potato chips inside.
>Eat them?
>Yes.
>You take a potato chip..... And EAT IT!
LeonGroff2777 hace 8 meses 10  
>You opened the fridge.
>There's some green vegetable juice inside.
>...Drink it?
>Yes
>...You don't know why, but you suddenly feel like running around and singing "PO-PI-PO-PI-PO-PO-PI-PO" at the top of your lungs.
>...
>...You should﻿ probably go to bed.
Rendivaunci hace 8 meses 25  
> you open the fridge door
> you see a potato chip
>....eat it?
>>Yes
>no
> you at a potato chip﻿
FusionAJ93 hace 8 meses 3  
> Open Youtube video
> Comments full of arrows.
> JOIN IN.
> ???
> Profit.﻿
sarah1232343 hace 8 meses 13  
This game was so thoroughly enjoyable that I have looked up its soundtracks on youtube.
Really Fantastic and one of﻿ the very best RPG games if you play it all the way through (with best ending).
SaiyanStrong hace 8 meses
this games so great that it has its﻿ own cd! i have it! best songs ever
ShowFizzle en respuesta a SaiyanStrong (Mostrar el comentario) hace 8 meses
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a﻿ school.
>Now it turns into strange giant tower!
>Eat it?
Onuralp774 hace 9 meses 56  
>you open the fridge
>theres a alarm clock left in there
>did dojima﻿ rush this morning ?
>....
>you feel that dojima will take it back to his room, you decide left it alone.
ZeroDragneel1 hace 9 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
MehTheBoy hace 9 meses 71  
hahahahahahah!!!﻿ yeeaah that ROCKS.
Shiraborough en respuesta a MehTheBoy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
when i 1st typed this i﻿ thought it would get thumbed down into oblivion...
MehTheBoy en respuesta a Shiraborough (Mostrar el comentario) hace 7 meses
wtf is wrong with you. what is this﻿ i dont even
cambone729 en respuesta a MehTheBoy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
have no idea. all i do know is its so crazy it got me﻿ top comment...
MehTheBoy en respuesta a cambone729 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 6 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
TClaymore hace 10 meses 2  
Omg, lol, I﻿ love you.
TheSuperbiasqualo en respuesta a TClaymore (Mostrar el comentario) hace 8 meses
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a strange flower.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>As you ate the flower, you see a boy in blue school uniform behind you glaring at you.
>He yells out﻿ 'Cross Fortune' and your vision becomes blurry...
VaatiOfDarkness hace 10 meses
Do you mean 'a boy﻿ with blue hair in school uniform'?
Persona3Line en respuesta a VaatiOfDarkness (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
No, it's a﻿ reference to Jun Kurosu in Persona 2
VaatiOfDarkness en respuesta a Persona3Line (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
>You open the fridge
>A single slice of ham lies alone on a paper plate in the middle of the fridge.
>The sight of it disturbs﻿ you.
>You decide to ignore it.
UreshiiInuElzah hace 10 meses 7  
>You open the fridge
>You find a﻿ fridge.
>...Open it?
>> Yes
>No
>You open the fridge.
>You find a fridge.
>...Open it?
Shintear hace 10 meses 14  
>>No﻿
MehTheBoy en respuesta a Shintear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
>﻿ ...You decide to go to bed.
> You have a dream in which you fall through an infinite number of fridges in an attempt to find the fabled Meat Dimension.
> ...You decide to lay off on the Rainy Day Specials for a while.
> Your Intelligence has increased!
Shintear en respuesta a MehTheBoy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses 2  
>...you suddenly felt hungry.
> go eat the rainy day special?
> yes
>no
>>YES
>...
>...
>... what the fuck were you﻿ thinking...
MehTheBoy en respuesta a Shintear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
> You find your path blocked by a fridge.
> ...Open the fridge?﻿
Shintear en respuesta a MehTheBoy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses 3  
>...your intelligence﻿ has went from QIUGFEQIUGFUQVW to IQOYERTBKA
MehTheBoy en respuesta a Shintear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
>You Opened the Fridge
>You see Shadow Kanji hanging out with naked men
>Join him?
>>>Yes
>No
>Your courage﻿ has increased from Coward to Daring
Sephiorth hace 10 meses 8  
>You open the ridge
>You see the only copy of Half-Life 2: Episode 3 inside...
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>Suddenly, you feel the urge to wield a crowbar instead of a katana.
>You are attacked by the﻿ Steam comunity!
GAME OVER
burnerthehedgehog hace 10 meses
No, just no bro. You suck at commenting.﻿
FourPartPlan en respuesta a burnerthehedgehog (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
i know...﻿
burnerthehedgehog en respuesta a FourPartPlan (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
>You open the fridge.﻿
>There's a strange object floating in the middle.
>Touch it?
>>YES
>You obtained Theory Cell.
>This is the substance the Temple has been looking for.
>You can exchange it for macca.
cupidonsarecreepy hace 10 meses en la lista de reproducción cupidonsarecreepy's favorites 8  
Win.﻿
TheSuperbiasqualo en respuesta a cupidonsarecreepy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 8 meses
Funny, I do too also go to the fridge when I get﻿ home even though I know there is nothing in there.
Onoku1690 hace 10 meses
> You open the fridge.
> You see an unreleased Play Station Console.
> Play it..?
>>YES
> You decided to play the game.
> A rush of deja vu comes to you all at once as the game boots!
> As﻿ you load the save file in the game, you realized a mini version of Yu is waving at Yu!
> .. You switched off the game and went to bed.
MystiKsGAME hace 10 meses 3  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
I want this song to play perpetually when I'm﻿ inside my house, unless I'm sleeping or watching a turned off tv at midnight.
ace0135 hace 11 meses
Has anyone else noticed that in Catherine it's implied that the tower is tartarus?
It even goes by p3 rules with Vincent going at night and not have memory of it afterwards like﻿ non-persona users.
JDWtri hace 11 meses 10  
something about﻿ Atlus man. such a winner :)
MayerEO hace 11 meses
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a gun inside.
>... Shoot yourself in the head?
Yes
>>>No
>... You﻿ decided not to make a reference.
imvufan123 hace 11 meses 71  
>You opened the fridge
>You see a sandvich
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>You﻿ regained 180+ Health
>You have a sudden urge to grab a minigun and go out and kill tiny cowards.
BluntmanEXE hace 11 meses 13  
its﻿ funny how the songs I actually like aren't on the sountrack :/
BunnyReaperBoo hace 11 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
katufatoomuch hace 11 meses
He said/ I’m the one who’s got to leave I said/ nobody’s really got to leave coz/ I don’t hear enough explanation/ all I need is admiration /big frustration bro he goes/ life is shor we gave a shot/ but﻿ didn’t work honey coz we had/ a whole lot going on and on/ and on…
katufatoomuch hace 11 meses
Signs of live﻿ overshadowed by dreams
Baby, don’t worry coz you ain’t alone
Only time running days without nights
Tears pass through
katufatoomuch hace 11 meses 6  
Every time look at the picture in the frame
Gaze in fascination﻿ so hard
You still think that is nothing but love
Rain still fals'.
katufatoomuch hace 11 meses 6  
Song: Gimmie your hearts!
Girl1:is that.. is that a like button?!
Guy1: I'd HIT IT﻿
Letsdraw123 hace 11 meses 10  
I think I heard Stupei somewhere o.o﻿
Yasmimm2011 hace 11 meses
>You realize that you havent really eaten anything for the past few days
>You open the fridge.
>A variety of﻿ different foods line the fridge doors however...
>Nothin catches your eye.
> . . . You should probably go to bed.
ShowFizzle hace 11 meses 3  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
DakkoX hace 11 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
DakkoX hace 11 meses
> You opened the fridge
> ZOOOOOLLLLLL!
>....
> You closed the fridge﻿
DakkoX hace 11 meses
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
dylanneill hace 11 meses
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge.
>You see Nanako's science project.
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>Nanako fails science
>Justice Arcana reversed﻿
DarkMage493 hace 11 meses
>You opened the fridge
>"I need yur HALP !!"
>...
>...Make lunch﻿ for tomorrow?
Saranyaaful hace 11 meses 3  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Every time I open﻿ my fridge to make lunch,I think of this song.
DarqueMinato hace 11 meses 7  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a cigarette pack belonging to Dojima.
>...Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You ate the pack of cigarettes
>You don't feel well...
>You decide to go﻿ to bed and try to forget this horrifying experience.
>...
>You hear Dojima yelling at you late at night.
TheDoctorPayne hace 11 meses 10  
Wellkum Bahk!﻿
hotwhire hace 11 meses
just﻿ beauty
pkmaster1984 hace 11 meses en la lista de reproducción More videos from Slayer0
I'M GOING TO GET THAT SON OF A BITCH﻿ WHO KEEPS DROPPING SHIT ON THE FLOOR, FUCKING SHIT I SPENT OVER 40 HOURS HAVING TO DEAL WITH THIS BULLSHIT IT ENDS NOW
childprey69 hace 1 año
>You﻿ watch this video.
>You think of some sort of refrigerator joke.
>Post it?
>Yes
>>>No
I'm going with no.
Ryuusei94 hace 1 año
>You open the fridge.
>You took out a glass eye and threw it in.
>...
>Nothing catches your﻿ eye.
VaatiOfDarkness hace 1 año 116  
FFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFF­FFFFFF PUNS﻿
Timblesink en respuesta a VaatiOfDarkness (Mostrar el comentario) hace 8 meses
> You open the fridge.
> You see a lemon inside.
> Eat it? >> Yes > No
> You ate the lemon.
> ..?!
> For some reason, you feel like burning the house down!
> Burn? >> Yes > No
> You burnt Dojima's house down. Nanako was caught in the fire as well and has to go to the hospital. Shame﻿ on you.
MystiKsGAME hace 1 año 6  
"You decided to watch the﻿ Midnight Channel."
Yukiko: "Guess who's wearing her kitty panites!"
Yosuke: DUUUUUUUDE!
Ryagan hace 1 año 9  
>You walk past the fridge in the kitchen. You hear gigglin coming from inside.
>Walk away
>>Open it.
>You see Chie and Yukiko inside. They stop and look at you.
>Ask what they are doing.
>Tell them to leave.
>>Join them.
>Your Courage﻿ has greatly increased.
>You spent a time with Chie and Yukiko...
PwnDealer hace 1 año 15  
....SHUT UP﻿ AND TAKE MY MONEY
MehTheBoy en respuesta a PwnDealer (Mostrar el comentario) hace 4 meses
> You open﻿ the fridge.
>There's a small animal inside.
>It growls at you.
>....Eat it?
zmanroc hace 1 año 6  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
I﻿ don't know why but I like listening to this while doing homework.
tija1012 hace 1 año
1:04 "everytime I cut the bitch in the face"﻿
MABASPLO hace 1 año 65  
I﻿ see you were just on /v/.
darklightfighter en respuesta a MABASPLO (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
shit someone noticed...﻿ but I was on /a/
MABASPLO en respuesta a darklightfighter (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Oh shit, that's right it was /a/, I was just﻿ thinking of /v/.
darklightfighter en respuesta a MABASPLO (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
you had no idea how much your comment contributes to﻿ my day. :)
GhettoElectroFU en respuesta a MABASPLO (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
everytime﻿ look the picture in the sand
Andelin09 en respuesta a MABASPLO (Mostrar el comentario) hace 8 meses
>You open the﻿ fridge door.
>Get on the floor.
>Everybody walk the dinosaur
imvufan123 hace 1 año
>You﻿ open the fridge
>You see the Velvet Room
Igor - Welcome to the Velvet Room!
>Eat it?
ShiyanCassius hace 1 año 21  
...Huh.﻿
RyotaroDojima hace 1 año
>You open the fridge.
> .﻿ . . Nothing Catches your eye.
> Close fridge?
>>> Yes
>>no
> You close the fridge
> Your courage has increased greatly!
> . . . You should probably go to bed.
ShowFizzle hace 1 año 2  
what's with﻿ the fridge stuff?
theonlyalex761 hace 1 año
play persona 4 then you will understand﻿
ItalianoDude23 en respuesta a theonlyalex761 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
> You open the fridge.
> You see Saki Konishi fighting.. some sort of demon with a Jack Frost?
> ...
> You try again.
> Now you see some guy in a coffee shop who beckons you to come in.
> You also see weird symbols floating around his head.
> ...
> You decided﻿ to leave the fridge alone.
MystiKsGAME hace 1 año
>You open the fridge.
>You see a copy of Persona 3 FES inside.
>.....
>Play it?
>>>Yes.
>No.
>You see both endings.
>Your Courage has greatly﻿ fallen.
twisterkid99 hace 1 año 8  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open﻿ the fridge.
>Everbody get on the floor.
>Everybody walk the motherfucking dinosaur
KirkJohnson34 hace 1 año
>You Opened the Fridge
>There's a Pair of Pink Polka-dotted Boxer Shorts inside, wear﻿ them?
>>YES
>No
>You put on the Boxer shorts and went to bed.
>You had a Dream that you were a Sheep climbing up a giant tower of blocks running away from things that are related to some woman you don't know.
>Your Intelligence increased!
Natendowii hace 1 año 93  
lol catherine!﻿
hazwan149 en respuesta a Natendowii (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Vincent: THat's weird... am i﻿ free already? next night: FuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuCK
beforeTHEmomentGIRL en respuesta a Natendowii (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
> You﻿ open the fridge.
> You see Adachi hanging out with his bitches and whores.
> Join him?
>>>>>Yes
>>No
CapitanKurosaki hace 1 año 14  
>You open the fridge.
>There's Kool-Aid Man inside.
>Drink﻿ him?
>>OH YEAH
>No
SammEater hace 1 año 13  
>You open﻿ the fridge.
Junpei: S'up dude? :D
>... Eat him?
>>Yes
>No
takeyb0y2 hace 1 año 25  
Este comentario ha recibido demasiados votos negativos. mostrar
coolcosmo3000 hace 1 año
>You open the fridge
>You find a list full of﻿ lame fridge comments
>Complain about it?
>>>Yes
>>No
>you proceed to post multiple hate comments in the comments section while accumulating thumbs downs each time you do.
>. . .You should probably go to bed
ShowFizzle hace 1 año 64  
the fridge represents﻿ my life
Antiformed en respuesta a ShowFizzle (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
XD﻿
ShowFizzle en respuesta a Antiformed (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
>You opened the fridge
>You see tiger blood and 7gram rocks.
>......Party?
>.....You somehow became Charlie Sheen pwn all﻿ bosses
chris63336 hace 1 año 3  
The weirdest thing just happened! I left my room and remembered that i had my mouse on a suggested video ready to click when i got back. But when i sat back down i noticed that my mouse was now hovering over the like button! i proceeded to click﻿ it. It was destiny!
ShowFizzle hace 1 año 3  
YES!﻿
gamemaster0422 en respuesta a leon4000 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Man, if the MC were living in MY house,﻿ I'd always have lots of fun puting all sorts of weird crap into the fridge just to see if he eats it!
Dominator150395 hace 1 año 15  
>You open the fridge.
>you see a pair of sunglasses.
>you decide to head *puts on sunglasses* straight to bed.
....
>you wake up in the middle of the﻿ night hearing someone yell "YEEEEAAAAAH!"
RaccoonXEspanosa hace 1 año 17  
whats with all the fridge comments??﻿ did the top 1 happen... sounds like it did??
Puresupremedarknesss hace 1 año
Este comentario ha recibido demasiados votos negativos. mostrar
GSNRecords en respuesta a Puresupremedarknesss (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
no it's just making fun of﻿ stuff
nianicole824 en respuesta a Puresupremedarknesss (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Is it me or are 99% of the viewers here to read the comments rather than listen to the the﻿ song?
DarqueMinato hace 1 año 22  
I'm that﻿ 1%. hehe
dissident93 en respuesta a DarqueMinato (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Eat﻿ Nanako's pudding? I mean what.
KingSesmu hace 1 año
>You open the fridge.
>You hear the distant sound of chains from within.
>Inspect?
>>>Yes
>No
Rise: Death is﻿ coming! Get out of there!
O.O
RaccoonXEspanosa hace 1 año 6  
Can't unhear the﻿ golfball dropping into the hole.
Casey Ormond hace 1 año
Why didn't this song make﻿ the soundtrack included with the game??? D=
DramaPimp06 hace 1 año
HEY WATCH MY PERSONA 4 TRIBUTE ON MY﻿ CHANNEL!!!!!!!!!!!!!
TheShadowDragonTeam hace 1 año
THE CHANNEL IS﻿ INYOH32
TheShadowDragonTeam en respuesta a TheShadowDragonTeam (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
i﻿ swear when Nanako said 'I love yo big bro!" i felt like giving her a hug
juicedup14 hace 1 año
None of this comments have nothing to do﻿ with this song
RPGIndustry hace 1 año
You opened the fridge.
You hear a voice.
"I am thou... and thou art I... Thou art the one who opens the [refrigerator] door..."
You decide to﻿ unravel a mystery.
blightedpersona hace 1 año 10  
> You opened the fridge.
> It looks the same﻿ as ever inside.
Almost cried when I read it.
Colgax hace 1 año 15  
> You open the fridge.
> There's a﻿ piece of burnt bread on a plate.
> Eat it?
>> Yes
> No
> You suddenly hear a familiar voice screaming in pain..
> You also hear the sound of chains..
DEATH IS NOT A HUNTER.
MystiKsGAME hace 1 año 8  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the﻿ fridge
>You see a red and white mushroom with eyes
>.......eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>You eat the mushroom and black out
>You awake five years later in a post apocalyptic world
GAME OVER
kemix1006 hace 1 año 10  
>You open the fridge
>you find some ingredients, and instantly start making chocolate pudding
Nanako: Big Bro, what are you doing?
Souji: Making chocolate pudding
Nanako: But its 4 A.M., why are you making chocolate pudding?
Souji: Because I have no control of my life
Souji: Heres your chocolate pudding Dojima
Dojima: Oh thats ok Nephew Souji, im not hungry﻿ anymore.
Souji:*AAAAAAHHHHHHHH!*
Ashbigbear hace 1 año 27  
Rugrats?﻿
Andru157 en respuesta a Ashbigbear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
10 internets to you, good sir.﻿ I'll make it 20 if you posted this at 4:00 AM.
mementomori39 en respuesta a Ashbigbear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
You opened the fridge.
You see QB inside.
...Contract?
Yes
>No
You decide to head straight to bed.﻿
shewhodoesnothing hace 1 año 9  
It's not for you, it's for Nanako! ／人◕ ‿‿﻿ ◕人＼
Pikalina en respuesta a shewhodoesnothing (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 4  
ARE YOU CRAZY THATS KYUUBEY!﻿
lordslifer666 en respuesta a Pikalina (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>....
>you closed the fridge
GOODNIGHT﻿ I AM GOING STRAIGHT TO BED.
darren886 hace 1 año 6  
>You opened the fridge
>You see bin latin
>eat him?
>Yes
No
You﻿ killed osama
...
I know....its lame
johjohjoh3 hace 1 año
if only that happened﻿ lol
chris63336 en respuesta a johjohjoh3 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>You see a cookie inside.
>Eat it?
>Yes
No
Ah-nuld calls and tell you to PUT﻿ THAT COOKIE DOWN! NOW!
BluntmanEXE hace 1 año 2  
i put this on play by my door so when i walked in this﻿ would play :)
gamemaster634 hace 1 año
>You﻿ open the fridge.
>You see Yukiko by the kitchen smiling at you with an apron on.
>Return to your room and sleep?
>>>Yes
>No
>*Courage Greatly Increased!*
>For some reason you expect a fierce storm tomorrow morning.
kinsuya1 hace 1 año 5  
You open the fridge.
You see namatame adachi izanami and amego sagiri
Why are you makeing a desition get the hell out﻿ of here!!!
gamemaster634 hace 1 año
>You go onto youtube.
>There seems to be a multitude of comments parodying off﻿ of the decisions you make in Persona 4.
>Read them?
>>>Yes
>No
*Mood increased! :D*
rorshachfan hace 1 año 43  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
Ashbigbear hace 1 año
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
Coppo68 hace 1 año
>You opened your laptop
>You see Persona 4 song﻿ on YouTube
>Play it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You like the video and favourited it...
*Courage increased!*
DiarySG hace 1 año 8  
"You decided to watch TV....but there's a justin bieber concert in﻿ every stations......You decided to watch DVD....only to find out "TWILIGHT" is the only one available......You decided to read a book instead..... But it's a harry potter book....F*** it, you just decided to watch YouTube."
asuna07neros hace 1 año
>You open the fridge
>You see an MP3 player, playing a tune which strangely fits the situation.
>...Continue﻿ listening?
>>>Yes
>No
For some reason, the tune makes you feel very patriotic...
...
You decided to go home and be a family man.
RikusV2 hace 1 año 19  
You opened the fridge.
Inside is a... thing. An abomination. Something not constrained by﻿ euclidean geometry or even this puny universe's physics. Merely a glance at it would drive any sane man into raving madness!
... Eat it?
>Yes
No
Well, if you're actually going to eat it, that must mean you are insane to begin with, so it has not effect on you. Though you do have a greenish-purple taste stuck in your mouth for the next few days.
Restraz hace 1 año 8  
i'm guessing﻿ the food is Mystery food X.
MrBrawler16 en respuesta a Restraz (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You opened the﻿ fridge
>You see steak
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You ate the steak, Chariot Arcana reversed...
pwinzy hace 1 año 74  
why you eat﻿ Chie's steak
supermariosonica en respuesta a pwinzy (Mostrar el comentario) hace 11 meses
Nanako: Welcome home, big bro!
Awwww... I wish﻿ her soooo much, i hope Persona 4 was real life... I don't care if I need to fight the goddess, I just want Nanako-chan! *cries*
ReyNixz hace 1 año
yeah and if﻿ it was granted there WILL be a possibility that YOU will either be killed or get into the Midnight Channel and murder someone and meet your Shadow
sora412zx en respuesta a ReyNixz (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Okaeri,﻿ onii-chan!
animangamania hace 1 año
You open the fridge...
you yoske eating you leftovers...
He growls
Walk away﻿ alowly
Call the police
>join him
gamemaster634 hace 1 año 5  
Let's not forget﻿ about Nero Ashbigbear, lol.
MrArcananox hace 1 año
EAT THE﻿ GRASS
ALL DAY
EVERY
DAY
ConkerfanX hace 1 año 15  
>You open the fridge.
>It's full of food.
>You feel a tasty bond between you and Fridge that can never be﻿ replaced.
>Spend time with Fridge?
>>Yes
>You ignored Nanko's staring all evening as you nommed on all of the food inside.
VaatiOfDarkness hace 1 año 198  
Congratulations! You﻿ can now make the ultimate persona of the Refrigeration Arcana, REFRIGERADON!
Tacklevines en respuesta a VaatiOfDarkness (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You open the fridge >there are lots of figurines from various games and animes >There is Lelouc, Ichigo, Zero, Firion and the﻿ black ranger from power rangers to name but a few >Play with them? >>>Yes >no > You play with the other characters, shouting out epic quotes from the various series >.... >You are pretty good at impersonating them Your EXPRESSION has Increased! >You start to feel awkward playing with toys, and go directly to bed to 'man' up.
Ashbigbear hace 1 año 2  
>You open the fridge. >You see most﻿ of a pizza in there. >Take it? >>YES >No >You take the pizza and eat some of it. >All of a sudden, you feel sick, and hear a woman talking. >You decided to look for your little sister, who is in a wheelchair. >She's in bed, so you decide to go monologue about how you'll make the world better in the mirror. >Your Charisma has increased! >You became Zero.
LeoJohnGalt en respuesta a Ashbigbear (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 3  
I guess that's one way to become a hero of Code Geass... The power of Pizza...﻿ XD
OtakuFreak08 en respuesta a LeoJohnGalt (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Welcome back﻿ big bro
MrHODEyoshi hace 1 año 11  
on a totally unrelated comment can anyone tell what the fan fare is called in﻿ this game when you finish a battle?
thekingofreyes3 hace 1 año
as strange as this sounds,﻿ the ost is called "period"
sheimisheimi1 en respuesta a thekingofreyes3 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
hey thanks! what a﻿ weird name for that song
thekingofreyes3 en respuesta a sheimisheimi1 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Welcome Back!﻿
MyHumanLife hace 1 año
you look at the comments﻿
you see the same joke over and over
nothing catches your eye
juicedup14 hace 1 año 21  
-You opened the fridge.
-The foods inside were﻿ insignificant.
-Because they were insignificant, you didn't eat them.
Amperschwa hace 1 año
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
matteste hace 1 año 9  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
However, if the Sun Social Link is maxed...
You open the fridge
You see Ayane in there
Ayane: Senpai...
"Eat" her?
>>Yes
No
You pull her out of the fridge and give her a hot drink. She indicates﻿ that she wants to spend the night....
You spent a long time with Ayane
omegathunderstorm hace 1 año
You open the fridge
You see Ayane in there
Ayane:﻿ Senpai...
"Eat" her?
>>Yes
No
You don't have a close enough bond for that action. You pull her out of the fridge, make her a hot drink and walk her home. She thanks you for all the help you give her and pulling her out of the fridge. She blushes violently while stammering
Sun Social Link Rank UP!
omegathunderstorm hace 1 año
You open﻿ the fridge
You see a loaf of bread
Eat the bread?
>>Yes
No
You ate the bread. While unappetizing, it did fill you up. You feel better for having finished eating the boring bread.
Diligence greatly increased!
omegathunderstorm hace 1 año 4  
>You open﻿ the fridge
>You see some tiger blood and 7 gram rocks inside
>Party?
>>Yes
>No
>You are now bi-winning!
MrLemoncholic hace 1 año 12  
>You﻿ open the fridge
>You find a can of Pringles and a Magneto Figurine
>Eat Pringles?
>>Yes
>No
>You suddenly sprout a curly mustache and feel the urge to punch the Magneto Figurine.
>Punch Magneto Figurine?
>>Yes
>No
>You just beat MagFuckingNeto! Fuck Da Knicks!
BigAlUpdates hace 1 año
LOL I bet only like 3 people who read that comment are gonna get﻿ that reference
MannyFresh1254 en respuesta a BigAlUpdates (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Makes sense. P4 protagonist and Zero have the same VA.﻿
KZN02 en respuesta a BigAlUpdates (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
You opened the fridge.
You see the ham grazing on the lettuce
..Eat it?
Yes
>>No
The Ham leaps out of the fridge and eats you!
Flash back to one day ago to set right what once went﻿ wrong?
omegathunderstorm hace 1 año 2  
>You open the fridge
>There is a single slice of ham﻿ lying on a paper plate alone in the middle of the fridge...
>The sight of it disturbs you...
>You decide to leave it alone
UreshiiInuElzah hace 1 año 10  
>You opened the fridge
>You﻿ see a potato chip inside
>............
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You take the potato chip.....and EAT IT!!!
zazry86100 hace 1 año 36  
>You﻿ opened the fridge
>You see Soviet Russia inside
>The fridge opened you
DIA333333 hace 1 año 55  
You opened the fridge
Dojima-san is freezing inside
Use Agidyne?
>>> Yes
you have﻿ toast dojima san. hereby the game cannot continue.
You have been summmoned to velvet room
Igor > why the hell you burn your uncle ? now the story can't go on!
do you eat igor?
>> yes
rnardbernardi hace 1 año 22  
Welcome﻿ back!
MrAnders0n2 hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge.
>You see﻿ a grue
>Eat it?
>Yes
>No
>You decided to eat the grue.
>You have eaten a grue, the feel of revenge is somewhat unsettling
>Courage has decreased
FallenWhiteSaber hace 1 año 7  
>You open the fridge
>You see that the fridge is empty
>Climb inside?
>>>Yes
>No
You climb inside and pretend to be a penguin,﻿ terrifying Nanako when she comes home with the groceries. After a long lecture from Dojima, you decide to go to bed and try to thaw out your toes.
MsFrazzledFro hace 1 año 199  
Eva﻿ reference with Pen Pen? Funny regardless. :)
SailorStarDust en respuesta a MsFrazzledFro (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Referencing what? I just made﻿ this up, lol :P
MsFrazzledFro en respuesta a SailorStarDust (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
I thought you were referencing Pen Pen from Neon﻿ Genesis Evangelion, but okay. Funny stuff either way heh.
SailorStarDust en respuesta a MsFrazzledFro (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
...that was the﻿ best suggestion ever. SUCH TIME WELL SPENT BEING A PENGUIN.
AoiYukinoMisharu en respuesta a MsFrazzledFro (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
LMAO!!! xD ﻿
TheFunGamer94 en respuesta a MsFrazzledFro (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
dont forget that your Knowledge and Understanding got﻿ a boost too :P
Pfoenixbrawler131 en respuesta a MsFrazzledFro (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You open the fridge
>You see a deathnote
>Take it
>>>Yes
>No
the Reaper appears behind u asking for an apple
You decided to give him﻿ on and head for bed
Diablokiller3 hace 1 año 4  
>You open the fridge
>it seems Dojima has made LOTSA SPAGHETTI!
>In fact the fridge is literally full of spaghetti
>You decide to help yourself until you cant stomach anymore
>you went to bed early, as you know what they say in Brooklyn; Early to bed, early to catch the worm... or is it﻿ the bagel?
Ashbigbear hace 1 año 9  
>You opened﻿ the fridge
>You spot an elevator inside
>Enter elevator?
>>Yes
>No
>You enter the elevator
>Sad piano music begins to play
Death is not a hunter unbeknow
rhymeswithgabriel hace 1 año 8  
> You opened the fridge
>You see a Jack Frost
> ...Eat it?
>>> Yes
>No
> You ate the Jack Frost.﻿ You hear "Hee-ho" echoing from your stomach.
> Your Charm greatly increased.
ToxicTeapot hace 1 año 11  
> You Opened the Fridge
> You see a bowl of ramen there.
Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
> You ate the ramen. You suddenly got the urge to start wearing Orange cloths, a headband with a leaf on it,carrie kunais,and yell form the rooftops that you are a ninja and shout "BELIEVE IT!" For no reason...
...
> You blame Yosuke and﻿ go to bed.
gohanRULEZ hace 1 año 20  
I see what﻿ you did there.
LeoJohnGalt en respuesta a gohanRULEZ (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
I'm happy﻿ someone did.
gohanRULEZ en respuesta a LeoJohnGalt (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>theres a fridge inside
>open﻿ it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You opened the fridge
>theres a fridge inside...
Ashbigbear hace 1 año 43  
reading all these comments made by﻿ day. keep em comin guys :D
pheromonekid hace 1 año 7  
great song﻿ to wake up to
thekingofreyes3 hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge. >You saw Dojima inside. >Eat it? >>>Yes >No >You decided to spend some time eating Dojima. >...... >You need enough Knowledge to find out how to finish the huge body. >You need enough Courage to eat a human. >You need enough Understanding in order﻿ to know whether how to eat Dojima. >...... >You failed to finish the Dojima. >You felt extremely pain in your stomach. >......ARGHHHHHH !! >You find out that what you eat is actually a shadow. >You've become a shadow, GAME OVER
IgnacioCryptmaw hace 1 año 5  
As awesome﻿ as this song is, i'm actually being more entertained by reading through these comments :'D
Sirloinsalot1 hace 1 año 8  
>You opened the fridge. >You see a meme inside. It seems rather old and forced. >Eat it? >>>Yes >No >You﻿ ate the meme >Knowledge decreased >Courage decreased >Understanding decreased >Expression decreased >Suddenly, you ´ve got the strange feeling to harass people on the internet. >You closed the fridge and decided to go to bed
AVoidDance hace 1 año 2  
>You open teh fridge
>There is cake...
Eat it?
>Yes
>>>No
>You decide not﻿ to eat delicious and moist cake, for fear of it being a lie
Ashbigbear hace 1 año 27  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a lonely sandvich sitting on a plate.
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>Suddenly you hear loud footsteps behind you,﻿ next thing you know all your blood was punched out and your spine was broken.
>......
>You were dominated by Heavy Weapons Guy!
GAME OVER.
/sobs
xXPitsLittleAngelXx hace 1 año 11  
I don't get any of these comments. What's with the "Greater Than" signs being used to indent the narration of a﻿ small script?
Cesariono hace 1 año
Because that's how it is﻿ in the game.
cosmiclucky en respuesta a Cesariono (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a Magatama inside the fridge.
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You have just noticed that there green marks in your body and you have﻿ become a demon!
rpgguy999 hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge.
>All your favourite food is inside.
>You feel a﻿ bond growing between you and the fridge.
>Souji has formed the Aeon Social Link with the Fridge!
>You spent some time with the fridge and after Dojima wondered if you need counseling, you went to your room.
VaatiOfDarkness hace 1 año 38  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see weird Al Yankovic stuck inside.
>Eat it?
>Yes
>No
>You decided not to eat it.
Weird Al lets out a sharp cry: EAT IT!!!! EAT IT!!!!!!
>You feel totally confused.
>Your﻿ weirdness has increased!
>You closed the fridge and decided to go to bed.
MeinKaracterALEX hace 1 año 9  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge
>You see﻿ moldy bread inside
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
>No
>You need less *Knowledge* to do this
PieMoe hace 1 año 15  
>You opened the fridge
>...you see something that resembles a breadstick in the back...
...eat it?
>>Yes
>No
...you began to eat the breadstick, but you heard﻿ a familiar man's voice cry out in pain...
...
You decide to head straight to bed.
cosmiclucky hace 1 año 2  
What is that a reference﻿ to?
TheIncompetentia en respuesta a cosmiclucky (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Igor's nose. ﻿
cosmiclucky en respuesta a TheIncompetentia (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
You opened the fridge.
You see a foldable bike inside.
...Ride it?
> Yes
No
Professor Oak's words echoed in﻿ your head...
"There's a time and place for everything! But not now."
...
You decide to head straight to bed.
Bushido1180 hace 1 año 224  
My﻿ internets. you may have them.
Skywolf17 en respuesta a Bushido1180 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 10 meses
opened the﻿ fridge
you see a tarsier inside
eat it?
>yes
no
O_O
catbuffalo hace 1 año
>you opened the fridge.
>you see a wild pokemon inside.
>Eat it?
>>>Yes
No
Your courage increased.
However...you see a﻿ red cap kid behind you.
you decide to head straight to bed
gdude82 hace 1 año 7  
0:40 "She don't give﻿ a shit.."
MaidOfBoarDome hace 1 año 6  
Delicious Nanako grass in fridge﻿ is delicious: YOU MUST EAT IT!
>OMNOMNOMNOMNOM
>...
>Your Courage has increased.
Andyilmatto hace 1 año
> You opened﻿ the fridge
> You see a Fsteak.
>......eat it?
> Yes
> Chie has appeared! STEAKSTEAKSTEAKSTEAKSTEAK!
> The Chariot social link has been reversed...
getar12345 hace 1 año 13  
ROFL﻿
gdude82 en respuesta a getar12345 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
did anyone notice the persona 3 calender on his﻿ bedroom wall
ammy8281 hace 1 año
you opened the fridge.
you see the videogame persona 3 inside.
.....eat it?
yes.
......
you realize you just ate the past itself and﻿ created a time paradox that will probably affect future events.
you decide to head straight to bed.
chidori901 hace 1 año 8  
Lyrics: suns above only shut does my please baby doll only coz your way oho only time my beat is speed of light please has too - says: I'm da one - who has got to leave you said: nobodys willing to got to leave coz I don't giving up-formation allbody is a miration pospuration ! hitting /$(§/)=()§##* going star face (show we give a shot) data work (honey goes) we had a whole﻿ load going on and on and on
Rollercoaster16 hace 1 año
>You﻿ open the fridge.
> You're not sure why you did that
*shuts fridge*
TempestDacine hace 1 año 6  
@Shitsocash Persona 3﻿ reference for the win.
WoWFanX hace 1 año
what the hell is with all this " you open﻿ the fridge and see.... ?? "
jeferrell hace 1 año
You should know it if you've played the game...Howewer, if you really don't know, this song is played in the house of the main character; while you're in the house you can open the fridge and eat something that may increase﻿ your courage.
Mangafun93 en respuesta a jeferrell (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You Opened the Fridge
>There's﻿ a pair of sunglasses inside
>Will you wear them? >Yes/No
>You took the Sunglasses out of the fridge. It seems this case...
>You put the shades on. ....Just got a lot cooler
>Your understanding increased!
>You hear a voice in the distance going "YEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!"
Natendowii hace 1 año 21  
You opened the fridge. You see an old N64 cartridge. There's something on it: YOUR TURN Play it? >Yes No ... something tells you you shouldn't have done that. You decide to head straight to bed. You dreamt﻿ about drowning. Your Courage increased!
KyrieFortune hace 1 año 6  
>You open the fridge
>You see a note
>Jump on the Bandwagon of people who are trying﻿ to be funny with the fridge jokes even if you're not funny?
>Yes
>>>No
You created a paradox because you are also trying to jump onto the bandwagon. Your hypocrisy has significantly increased.
WoWFanX hace 1 año 19  
>You opened the fridge. >There's a Shadow in it. >Upon closer inspection, it looks like a copy of you. >Shadow Souji flipped the bird at you. >Punch it? >>Yes >No >You punched your other self. >Shadow Souji was defeated! >...However, you just﻿ punched you parallel self, so you felt the pain of your strong punch. >You began to understand what it means to be your other self. >Your Understanding significantly increased.
SolFZ hace 1 año 2  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a deck of cards and a motorcycle.
> ...Card Games on Motorcycles?
>>CARD GAMES ON MOTORCYCLES!
>Screw the Card Games, I have Persona!
>You tried playing a card game﻿ on a motorcycle but without a Duel Disk system you crash into Yosuke's bike.
>REVERSED Magician Link
VaatiOfDarkness hace 1 año 12  
>You opened the fridge
>You see a Yugioh reference
...Burn?
>>Yes
>No
Your Expression significantly increased.
You decide to head﻿ straight to bed.
Serieth en respuesta a VaatiOfDarkness (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 2  
You﻿ opened the fridge.
You see a laptop playing a Youtube video.
...Play it?
>>Yes
No
...
You now keep wanting to sing about "Signs of love, overshadowed by dreams".
Your Expression has increased!
VaatiOfDarkness hace 1 año 2  
> You opened the fridge.
> For some reason, there's an alarm clock inside, ticking away...
> Was Dojima in a rush this morning...?
> ...You﻿ left it alone.
TheHijackreaper hace 1 año 9  
I feel like I remember that,﻿ and then at the same time it sounds like a joke.....
nonnatural en respuesta a TheHijackreaper (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
It's actually one of the﻿ commands from the game. :D
TheHijackreaper en respuesta a nonnatural (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
You open the fridge.
nothing catches your eyes.
Sleep inside?
>>Yes
>No
You decided to sleep inside the fridge.
Your "Coolness" has﻿ increased.....XD
frozenmache11 hace 1 año 16  
> You opened﻿ the fridge.
> Your HP has decreased!
gs68 hace 1 año
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
I can﻿ hear the error sound in this song
Cmbheadquarters hace 1 año
DAY 1:
You opened the fridge.
Nothing catches﻿ your eye.
DAY 2:
You opened the fridge.
Nothing catches your eye.
DAY 3:
You opened the fridge.
Nothing catches your eye.
Artyon5 hace 1 año 2  
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
IzanagiAnime hace 1 año 2  
And nobody ate that night~﻿
TheCenarkah hace 1 año 2  
>You opened the fridge.
>Chuck Norris was﻿ inside fighting Ameno-Sagiri.
>Bet on who?
>>Chuck Norris
>Ameno-Sagiri
>Chuck Norris used Roundhouse Kick.
>9999 damage to Ameno-Sagiri.
>>Chuck norris wins!
SilverInnocence hace 1 año
can somebody﻿ tell me the nameof the artist of this song?
Wasser123123 hace 1 año
The﻿ composer is Shoji Meguro. The singer is Shihoko Hirata.
otakughost en respuesta a Wasser123123 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Everyday's great﻿ at your Junes!! ~<3
luv4Aerith hace 1 año 2  
Welcome home big﻿ Bro!
SchabonHatHunger hace 1 año 4  
>You﻿ open the fridge.
>You sense an intensely terrifying presence!
>An enemy jumped out!
MC: Oh, Crap...
KrimzonFlygon hace 1 año 2  
You opened the fridge
You﻿ see a gun inside
...Shoot yourself?
Yes
>>No
You decide not to make a continuity reference.
ZaneBarrow hace 1 año 103  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a half empty bottle with a warning label:
>WARNING: Drinking this substance will lead to upset stomach of stomach and may even cause﻿ serious injury, keep out of reach of small children.
>...
>Drink it?
>>Yes
>No
RyushiTR hace 1 año 2  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see an odd toaster inside.
>Take it out and make some toast with﻿ it?
>>>Yes
>No
It turns out to be a Thanatoaster. You burned your bread.
"Life is truth, and never a dream... All souls know this from birth..."
CMDmusic hace 1 año 136  
Epic﻿ LULZ
Wyrmcrush en respuesta a CMDmusic (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Best﻿ puns ever.
FenixSeraph en respuesta a CMDmusic (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
BURRRRN﻿ MY BREEEAAADDDD
declinefan en respuesta a CMDmusic (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 5  
>You open the fridge.
>There's a PS2 controller in there.
>Use﻿ it?
>>Yes
>No
>You suddenly feel more in control of your life than usual.
Voxerik hace 1 año 25  
*you watch chie undress*
Chie: um...hey
*stares at you awkwardly*
You: nice﻿ ass
Chie: thanks
fierylava12 hace 1 año
I thought﻿ Naoto was p3 mc with a sex change
silentazian en respuesta a MalvaPura (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 2  
I﻿ thought Naoto was a guy until I heard his voice in the game.I was like There is no way this is a guys voice ow he is very very young lol
MalvaPura en respuesta a silentazian (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
urm u has to defeat Eribus or w/e his name is because eribus can just revive﻿ nyx -_-
mariox901 en respuesta a OEGSProductions (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
If i was in Persona 4, My Persona would be Chuck﻿ Norris. Hands down.
IzanagiAnime hace 1 año
so ur implying chuck norris isn't a existing﻿ being since all persona's are about mythical creatures and stuff.
mariox901 en respuesta a IzanagiAnime (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Akihiko's persona﻿ was Ceasar
he was real
JotunnTheImp en respuesta a mariox901 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
How can You Be so sure Ceasar Existed More than 1000 Year's Ago how can they be so accurate as to﻿ have information of someone and Have all This info on someone who died 1990+ Years ago so He can very well be a myth.
mariox901 en respuesta a JotunnTheImp (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
-_- troll...﻿
XxRokusasuxX en respuesta a mariox901 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Why thank you﻿ :D ur so kind
mariox901 en respuesta a XxRokusasuxX (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
side's Chuck Norris Exist because﻿ we know he doe's.
mariox901 en respuesta a JotunnTheImp (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Persona 4 has taught me that﻿ drinking expired milk that has turned halfway to yogurt increases your Courage.
I should try it.
Jesscookie1 hace 1 año 17  
You open the fridge...
You find Nanako's Science Project
...Eat it?
>>Yes
>No.
Your bastardness has increased.
"However,﻿ you aren't feeling well, so you decide to go to bed early..."
NataliePlz hace 1 año 3  
>You opened the fridge
>A man in a black cloak is sitting there drinking your uncle's beer and crying about "hearts".
>Drink it?
Yes
>>No
>You decided to wait for the Final Mix﻿ release.
prudence00 hace 1 año 10  
You open﻿ the fridge
CONGA!!!
...Join it?
YES! Pa-ra-rà!
Mangafun93 hace 1 año 6  
ah... i﻿ love second-person.
Mark Nguyen hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>A strange man jumped out at you!
>Tell Rorschach﻿ what he wants to know?
>>>Yes
>No
> Good plan there.
> You decide to go to bed early... but you can't sleep...
noobface4291 hace 1 año 13  
Try like a certin﻿ other 3 Protaganists
trickymander en respuesta a ExcaliburLost (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
you need﻿ to understand maybe he does not want to go but he have no choise,
trickymander en respuesta a shadowpepe (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
trickymander en respuesta a falcolegend (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Surprisingly, the MC can eat﻿ practically EVERYTHING in p4! xD
junhao63 hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>You see a can of whoopass.
>.....Eat it?
>>Yes
>You have acquired the persona "Chuck Norris." You may now win the game..or go to bed early.﻿
ZelosRaine hace 1 año
Este comentario se ha marcado como spam. mostrar
ZelosRaine hace 1 año
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
One time, I﻿ found a Souji x Yosuke yaoi doujinshi named "Signs of Love"...
And I just gotta say...
xD
YosukeHanamurasLOVE hace 1 año
>You open the fridge
>You see a figurine of Zeno of Elea holding a plate with delicious chocolate cake.
>Try reaching for it?
>> Yes
>﻿ No
> You die of old age trying to reach the cake, but only able to get half way of the distance, and half way of half way, and half way of half way of half way...
Voxerik hace 1 año 8  
That represents the infinite sum of (1/2)^x. The sum = 1. The protagonist does﻿ not reach the cake until infinity passes.
SmithyJones3 en respuesta a Voxerik (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You open the fridge
>You see a bottle of Dojima's whiskey
>Drink it?
>>Yes
>You suddenly hear a voice in your head
>"Be careful, I sense Death!!"﻿
Sartarus hace 1 año 11  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You opened the fridge.
>There's a Yukkuri!
>...you decided to﻿ close the fridge.
Platinumyo hace 1 año 10  
> You opened the fridge.
> You see a glowing blue ball, made of what appears to be glass. It's an Aque Blastia Core,﻿ and is used to power magical machinery, though you're not sure how you know all that.
> It has an otherworldly feel to it and is very obviously not food.
> ...Eat it?
>>>Yes
No
> Congratulations! Yuri Lowell has now HAD IT WITH YOU, MAN.
Memphismastermind hace 1 año 6  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see﻿ lemons.
>Strangely enough, you have enough ingredients to make lemonade.
BluntmanEXE hace 1 año
>You opened the fridge
>you﻿ find a beer
> Drink it?
>>Yes
No
> your courage is to low to touch Dojima's beer
royalealter02 hace 1 año 10  
>You opened the fridge
>You see your own universe inside of it
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>You and everyone else is instantly﻿ crushed by your teeth.
carmine741 hace 1 año 10  
Please stop,﻿ babeh.
Writtenjustice en respuesta a carmine741 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
>You open the fridge
>You find yourself in it
>Eat yourself?
>>Yes
>No
>You begin by eating your fingers, then hands, and then arms. You quickly﻿ die of blood loss.
carmine741 hace 1 año 9  
>You open the fridge
>You find some grass
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>You were arrested for﻿ eating pot, you poor dumbshit.
carmine741 hace 1 año 9  
>You opened the fridge
>You see a demon dog inside yelling﻿ "ZUUL, MOTHERFUCKER! ZUUL!"
>You shut the fridge, grab your cell phone, and call the Ghostbusters.
BluntmanEXE hace 1 año 17  
>You opened the fridge.
>You see a "Mara" figurine.
>...Upon closer inspection,﻿ Mara's figurine turns out to be flexible... like those women's equipments.
>...
>You decided to leave it inside.
shadowpepe hace 2 años 6  
>You opened the fridge.
>You found a stick of C4.
>..............
>You decided to put it in Nanako's backpack.
>Your "Bastardness" has greatly increased.
﻿
SolFZ hace 2 años 10  
@NegStarnite93 bcoz he appear in SMT:Nocturne.﻿
devilhacker86 hace 2 años
>you opened the fridge.
>you see a copy of the surfing bird cd. will you play it?
>yes
no
*nanako points gun in her mouth*
>1 week later.....
MC- Nanako, havent you heard!?
Nanako- about what?
Dojima- nanako, wait---!
MC- BIRD IS THE WORD!﻿
swordfish1390 hace 2 años 6  
You opened﻿ the fridge.
You see the videogame "Persona 4" inside.
...Play it?
>>Yes
No
....
You don't know why, but you feel like you've been controled by yourself...
You decide to head straight to bed.
Agusloquillo hace 2 años 51  
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
Este comentario ha recibido demasiados votos negativos. mostrar
catbuffalo hace 2 años
@catbuffalo
FF6 was better. And may I remind you who was responsible for most﻿ of the team's breakthroughs before Naoto got there?
Clue: it wasn't Chie.
reaperofthedamned07 en respuesta a catbuffalo (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años 9  
How DARE﻿ You!
ShadeCrenshaw en respuesta a catbuffalo (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
whaddyamean﻿
catbuffalo en respuesta a ShadeCrenshaw (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Everyday I get back, I check what's in the fridge lol﻿
Adventuredeath1 hace 2 años
Persona 4 has great songs... but I like this one the most.
Yes, I admit it: I sometimes just run around the living room to waste time while listening﻿ to this song. I don't know why I like it so much.
thattotally hace 2 años 3  
i think she say s something about,﻿ "...give a $h!t..." around :41.
kuraidjinn hace 2 años
Let's Give a Shot﻿ actually ;D
mariox901 en respuesta a kuraidjinn (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
OH! Cool, thanx. The OTHER﻿ lyric that i thought it was seemed...out of place. Thanks a lot!
-Best Regards-
kuraidjinn en respuesta a mariox901 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
actually i though so too but Japanese and their Engrish is hard﻿ to get at first....
mariox901 en respuesta a kuraidjinn (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
@mariox901 Yes, very true. Often when an Anime, theme song is translated from original Japanese lyrics to English lyrics, it usually makes little to no sense at all make. For example: The old series "Ranma 1/2." Have you ever looked @ the English subtitles for the opening theme? "...couple on a deck, don't make a scene, no no, heck i'm a nervous wreck, my shaking knees unforseen..." I mean, WHAT?!﻿
kuraidjinn en respuesta a mariox901 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año 2  
Oh hell, a worse example is Azumanga Daioh.﻿ "Beware the temptation of wheat" ....
MuroKhan en respuesta a kuraidjinn (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Wheat,﻿ Eh?
ULTIMADONUT en respuesta a MuroKhan (Mostrar el comentario) hace 1 año
Nanako- "Welcome home, Big bro!"
MC- thinking '^_^ That's what I look forward to eveyday when I come home from school of from the TV"
>opens fridge
>>There's nothing﻿ that catches your eye...
Souji- 'Darn it'
YukiTsukuyomi hace 2 años
>You open the fridge
>You see a model rocket
>There's note attached: To Russia
> Eat It?
>>Yes
>No
>Dee Dee Ramone comes back as a shadow and asks﻿ if you've heard about the word.
LeoJohnGalt hace 2 años
Comentario eliminado
Autor eliminado
>You come into the living room and notice a small record player next﻿ to Dojima. Odd. >You open the fridge. >There seems to be a newspaper inside. >You ask Dojima-san about it. Dojima: Hm? There was a paper in the fridge? Let me see it. >You grab the paper and hand it to Dojima-san. Dojima: Strange, I thought this paper would carry a certain ornithological piece. A story of an...avian variety. I mean, haven't you heard? >How strange...Ask him what he means? >>Yes >No Nanako: NO BIG BRO DON'T!
Voxerik hace 2 años 5  
I remember eating Nanako's﻿ science project.
XXF2XX hace 2 años
LMFAO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!﻿
XXF2XX en respuesta a arcanum59 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años
Souji:WHO YOU CALLING SEMPAI? ITS SENPAI!!!
Kanji:(in small voice) So-o-orrry...﻿
11wow111RETURNS en respuesta a BonkuriTokio112 (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años
she says it at 0:43 too﻿ :P
dennytothez en respuesta a UncleJemimahs (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años
will there be﻿ a reincarnation soundtrack for Persona 4?
TYREKJAMISON hace 2 años
I doubt it but that's be cool if they﻿ remixed this.:D
BonkuriTokio112 en respuesta a TYREKJAMISON (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años
Well, obviously they didn't ACTUALLY say that,﻿ it still sounds like it :P
UncleJemimahs en respuesta a thesunalwayrises (Mostrar el comentario) hace 2 años


----------


Aurainmaker
> You open﻿ the fridge.
> You find a block of C4.
> You decided to put it in Nanako's Backpack.
> Your "Evil Bastard" has significantly increased.


BiologicalClock
You opened the fridge. ...There's white miso. ...? You think that this used to be red miso, though... There is a package of red miso, but it is far past its expiration date. Eat it...? YES Your tongue hurts... Your eyes water from the﻿ odor... Your throat is burning... 



soraeyo
You open the fridge
You see that their is a﻿ well made sushi that say do not eat "MC"
You remove the sign and eat it anyway
your "Helping People" has increased greatly...





SilEntNiGHtPhanTom 
> You opened﻿ the fridge.
> There's a shadow in the fridge
> Eat a little, without telling your persona?
[Yes]   No





HappilyAnti 
>There's some peanut butter in the fridge
>...
>...Wait, what?
TRUE STORY LOL. Peanut butter﻿ doesn't go there, unfortunately.




dante10022003
>You opened the fridge
>You see a sheet of paper
>Read it?
[Yes]   No
>It's the lyrics﻿ to Your Affection.
>You realize that it's "Taking pride from fear" instead of "Get me some coffee".
>Your understanding has greatly increased.



TronDevlin
>you opened the fridge >you see a gun and a sheet of paper >the instructions say "Evoker" >you﻿ know what to do >do it? >yes no >you pull the trigger >you look to the left and see your brains on the wall >what an aweful mistake... >game over man... 

->
badflamer
adachi comes over and picks up the gun from your dead hands. "Dumbass." he turns to the camera. "Kids stop playing video games till 5 AM every night﻿ unless you want to end up like this fool."

[The more you know]



spongefan1
> You opened the fridge.
> You see﻿ a small pack of raccoons inside.
> ........................
> You cannot process what this could possibly be about.
> You decide to ignore it.





yummywaffles96
>You opened the fridge.
>Surprisingly, you found a copy of Persona 3! It's your lucky day!
>Then again, you begin to﻿ wonder why you have a strange sense of deja vu...
>..................
>Disturbed, you decide to leave it alone





marsmahboi 
I wanted to think of﻿ a cool comment like everyone else but I got something weird like,
>You open the fridge
>You see Yosuke stuck inside
>............
>Game Over



Quaquecyoe
>You open the fridge. >You see a smaller fridge inside..... >...... >Open it? >Yes No >Inside is another, even smaller fridge. >You continue opening fridges, each one containg an identical, yet slightly smaller, fridge. >............ >You starve to death, having spent 3 days opening refrigerators without finding any food. >...... >BAD END﻿ 




Gravelneed
>You opened the fridge
>You see Nanako's Pudding.
>.......
>Eat it?
>yes
no
>Your Courage﻿ has greatly increased.
>Your Understanding has greatly decreased.



AnetteSeraphitaVee
>You open﻿ the fridge
>You see an alarm clock ticking away
>was Dojima in a hurry this morning?
>...
>Eat it?
[Yes]   No
>You﻿ choke on the clockwork
> BAD END



Sephiko 
>You open the fridge
>You see the P4 soundtrack CD inside
>You remember that this song isn't on it
>. . . . . . .﻿ . . . .
>You decide to leave it there



kolangkaling10
 > you open the fridge > you see a can of baygon > who would have put it here...? > ..... > drink it? > yes no > holy cow....! its just tastes like Sprite Zero Sugar....! > Your Courage has reached its maximum level > Your Knowledge has reached its maximum level > However..... > You feel that your life is in peril & critical condition...... > ......... > You slumped to the ground with your﻿ mouth foaming.....





SilEntNiGHtPhanTom
> You﻿ opened the fridge.
>You saw somekind of portal inside it...
>Touch it?
>Yes
No.
> !!!! You were inside Mayonaka Fridge!! O.o
Im sorry for d randomness :D




>You opened the fridge.

>A sketchbook is in here with a picture of a﻿ guy with a goatee on the front page.

>....

>You decided to leave it alone.

VaatiOfDarkness




NarutoloverHinata
>You opened the fridge
> There is a bowel with miso in it...
>Something highly disturbs you about it
Eat It?
>......
Your stomach knew﻿ what you was trying to do and retaluated





VaatiOfDarkness
>You opened the fridge.
>It's extremely foggy inside...
>Your mind cannot process what is going on...
>You shut the fridge door and pretend everything﻿ is completely normal.




VaatiOfDarkness
>You opened the fridge...
>It's extremely foggy inside.
>You see a Shadow attempting to steal the cheese...
>You﻿ left it alone.





>There's a note on the refrigerator door....
>Dear MC, please don't eat my sandwich and rice. It's my lunch tomorrow. Thanks! ﻿ Dojima
>Eat the sandwich and rice
>Yes
>Since you ate Dojima's sandwich, he will remain mad at you for the remaining months. Thus, being unable to progress S.Link.
...ffffffffffffffuck!
lightskinboi06 


Casparatis
>You opened the fridge. >... >You noticed an azalea in a pot. >Eat it? >Yes >... > You feel a﻿ slight feeling of being eversed. You learned that word from this text message. Unfortunately, it reminds you of a certain platformer you played last night. >Your Expression has greatly increased. >Your Knowledge has greatly increased. >Your Understanding has greatly increased. >Your Courage has dropped to Level 1. >You feel that you must work off the nightmares in bed. 





>you opened the fridge
>you noticed a penguin secret animal cracker
will you eat it?
>yes
no
..........
before you had the time to eat it kanji smashed a chair at your head , stole﻿ your secret cracker, and raped you while you were unconscious....GAMEOVER!
Klausiancliff89





>you open the fridge
>there is a cup of pheromone coffe
>however you﻿ realize it rises charm and unlike
in persona 3 charm is not a parameter in game so...
>you decide to leave it alone
Klausiancliff89 





>You opened the fridge...
>There is a cake.
>Eat it...?
>Yes. No.
>The cake is a lie. You feel that you will﻿ never find the truth now. Fog swirls around your head...
Life is truth, and never a dream...
Selryam616 





>You opened the Fridge...
>You find a chocolate﻿ platipus.
>Eat it...?
>>Yes
>No
>The chocolate platipus was in fact made out of mud!
>You feel oddly good, in fact you feel stronger then ever!
>All Persona's Strength, Magic, Endurance, Agility and Luck have Increased by 10!
TearGrande 





>You open the fridge
>You notice there is heroin in the back
>O_o
>You suddenly question where your uncle has been for the past﻿ few nights
>You decided to leave it alone
wasnoperson 





>You open the fridge.
>The meaning of﻿ life is inside.
>...
>Eat it? ->Yes No
>The world will never know now. You feel like a tremendous douchebag.
Mank25 





>You opened the fridge.
>You see...a portable MP3 player and some cool headphones.
>Play﻿ it...?
>Yes.
No.
>There's only one song on it - a Burn My Dread remix.
>Come to think of it, this feels strangely like deja vu...
>You decided to steal it anyway.
VaatiOfDarkness 






>You open﻿ the fridge
>You see a soda
>Drink it?
>Yes
No
>You are now in the middle of the living room wearing a bikini, dancing and singing
>Nanako is now traumatized
catijusto69





> You open the fridge.
> There is a rock
> Eat﻿ it...?
>Yes
No
> You now want to burn you bread for some reason.
crapface108 






>You open the fridge
>You find the panda that is usually sitting on a box on the table.
>Eat it...?
>>Yes
>No
>You've lost your﻿ only true friend....
>Eat fridge?
BloodRedOath 



 Just got another fridge one: *You opened the fridge* *Adachi is talking with Dojima inside* *...Lick them?* >>Yes >No *Kanji burst in the door demanding﻿ Dojimas penguin cracker* *An epic battle occurs over the penguin* *Kanji wins, but the cracker is broken in two.* *Kanji proceeds to smash you head in with a chair and rape you while unconcious* Life is truth, and never a dream...
DarthMeg 





>It's late at night. What to do?
>Login to youtube
Go﻿ to bed
>You decide to login to youtube.
>You see the comments for the video: Signs of Love mimicking the text narration thats actually in game.
>You make a comment just like it
>Your diligence has gone up!
You decide to go to bed..
MrRaui 





>You opened the fridge.
>Inside is a locket with a strange content inside.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>No
>Your skin begins to split. You cough horribly as you feel a great mass move through your throat.﻿ You cough until you vomit a pile of blood.
>You aborted God! Diligence increased by 1.
neoswordmaster





>You open the fridge.
>You see a human head.
...
Eat﻿ it?
>Yes
>No
melovesmybuddies



 You open the fridge... There's a pack of animal crackers. ...Eat them? >>Yes The crackers are delicious!﻿ You go to sleep full of delight! >Expression increased! The next day... Kanji:Hey sempai, I think I left a pack of graham crackers over your house when I was helping Nanako with her craft project, Have you seen them? Yes No >>Run! Kanji: S-sempai?! Wait, What the hell! Why're there crumbs on your uniform!? Get back here!
BonkuriTokio112 



 > You opened the fridge. > Nanako is sitting﻿ in the fridge, talking to a toaster. >You have the ingredients to make Toasted Lolita Crackers. > Make lunch for tomorrow? >>Yes >No > You sliced Nanako up into waffles. How should you cook her? > Toast her lightly > Cover her in sake, then toast > Turn her into sushi and fry >> Leave the Nanako Waffles for Dojima > Your understanding has increased.
ChaosmusicEX 




 you open the fridge there's a big cake that Nanako left.. Eat it?? >>yes Your weight and your courage increased!! After coming hme frm﻿ school.. Nanako:Big bro,someone ate my chocolate cake..even i left a note on it! do u knw who ate it?? >Tell her the truth? >>>>NO nanako:You ate IT!!!!! UR TERRIBLE!
SakuraYuko97





"You opened the fridge"
"There is the number 42 written on a piece of cake"
"This feels oddly like a life or death situation"
"Eat a little, without telling the world?"
>>>YES
>NO
"You hear Igor saying "You have just eaten the crystal of power, which you have nurtured upon your journey."
"Come to think of it, isnt 42 the meaning of Life?"
"You kill﻿ yourself..."
Dojima: That was just my 42'nd birthday cake. Crazy imagination that kid had. No most questions from Inaba.
DarthMeg 





>You open the fridge
>You see﻿ a pair of underpants inside
>???
>Profit!
Makutus





>You open﻿ the fridge.
>You find Yosuke stuck inside.
>...
>Strangely, now you have enough ingredients to make Yosuke soup.
>Make lunch for tomorrow?
arcanum59

->

>You﻿ find Chie the next day.
>Share Yosuke soup with her?
>She says your Yosuke soup tasted a little immature and smelled like boy's cologne. She can't put her finger on who it reminds her of.....
rorshachfan





>You see bread﻿ in toaster.
>Burn it?
>Yes
>No
T94OWH 





> You open the fridge.
> You see bizarre blob of black slime.
> You remembered Spike Speigel coming over earlier in the year.
> .................
> Is this his﻿ Ganymede rock lobster?
> You quickly GTFO
omniwench8000





>You open﻿ the fridge.
>It´s empty.
>Eat it?
>Yes No
Springmaus2007




 >You open the fridge. >You find Kanji hiding from Naoto who wishes to kill him﻿ for seeing her naked in the bath. >Tell her? >Yes No >You close the fridge and call her on your cell. -5 hours later until midnight- >You hear sirens near your neighborhood. GAME OVER >Continue from a few hours back? New game*Why did I tell her again?*
kousakagami109





>You opened the fridge
>You see a weird living parasite.
>.....Eat it?
>>Yes
No
>You have become a Demi-Fiend, and Dante is after﻿ you.
T94OWH 





To eat or﻿ not to eat
this game's deep
apw28





"You opened the fridge"
"There is stack of money with eyeballs playing weird music"
Eat It...?
>>>Yes
>No
You﻿ suddenly have the urge to spend 15 minutes to save 15% on car insurance for a car you dont have yet.
"You decide to go to bed early..."
DarthMeg 





>You open the fridge.
>You find Rise's underwear from the party last night when she got drunk...
>......
>Sell them online?
>Yes
No
>You quickly ran to your room and logged onto eBay.
>You sold the underwear and made a﻿ great profit.
>............
>Throw another party and get Yukiko drunk?
JonnotheHedgehog 





 You feel an intensely terrifying presence coming from the fridge... ....Open the fridge? >>Yes >No Do you really want to open the fridge? >>Yes >No Something jumped out of the fridge! ....It was Rise. ....You are not amused by this. Punch Rise in the mouth? >Yes >>YES!! You punched Rise in the mouth. Social Link reverse.....but it was so﻿ worth it.
kazemaru95421 





>You open the fridge
>You see some mistery food X
>Eat﻿ iT?
No
>Yes
"Life is truth and never a dream"
entertainmentsteve 





>you opened the fridge.
>you see a small mouse rolling around in an empty jar of jelly.
>you get a strange sense of deja'﻿ vu.....
>,,,,,
>you decided to leave it be.
swordfish1390





>you open the fridge
>you nothing that catch your eyes
>what do you do?
close it
>WTH is this always empty?!
>you enter the fridge and find P3 MC.
P4 MC: wow so this is﻿ where he was...
MalvaPura





>You﻿ opened the fridge
>Suddenly, DICKS EVERYWHERE
BUDGETFREE





>You opened the fridge.
>You see an Exsphere.
>Equip it?
>>Yes
No
>You turned﻿ into an Exbelua. Now you're fucked.
VaatiOfDarkness





You﻿ open the fridge
You see a suppressant
...Take it?
>Yes
no
You end up like Shinjiro
gyminus23 





>You open the fridge.
>There's﻿ Nyx in a jar.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
No
>Congratulations. You have prevented the fall.
OEGSProductions 





You open the﻿ fridge...
There's a parasidic worm.
...Eat it?
>>Yes
You welcome the parasidic worm into your heart... literaly...
You don't feel well, you decide to go to the hospital.
RaiKanZu

->

It is made up of 16 segments.﻿ It turns into two segments when you cut it. Two more, over and over until you've got 16 of the little bastards running all over his body. NURSE, LASER!
reaperofthedamned07






Opened the fridge
You see a lemon inside
eat it?
>yes
no
Turns out it was nanako's﻿ head. You feel like a bastard.
catbuffalo




 You opened the fridge. Teddie is stuck inside. .... Eat him? >Yes No All﻿ of your stats have increased! =D However... You have now just broken the Star Social Link, thus being unable to create Personas of the Star Arcana. GAME OVER. NOOOOOOOOOOOO! XD
YosukeHanamurasLOVE






>You﻿ opened the fridge.
>You see mysterious green mold growing in the back.
>Eat it?
>>Yes
>...Your Thoughtless Stupidity has increased!
Yuuraki






You open the fridge...
There's bottle of milk way past it's expiration date
Drink it? >Yes >No
You drank the milk
......
......
......
You begin to feel dizzy, you hear a familar voice, a blurry﻿ figure like Teddie stands before you with a rape face.
You blacked out....
ANGRYMAPLE




 >You Opened the fridge you >you see a Hamburger. ...eat it? >yes >you go to sleep the next day... Teddie:I think i left a Hamburger at your house when i was playing with Nanako, Have you﻿ seen them? >Yes Teddie:Where is it then? >Point Stomach >Run Teddie:Rawr!!
11wow111RETURNS





>You opened the fridge
>You see a jar of pickled relish
>Eat it?
No
>>Yes
>You feel funny and decide to go to bed early
...>You dreamed that your uncle was using you as target practice for eating his relish that Nanako had bought﻿ for him.
DreamCloud10 



 you open the fridge there's a good-looking cake ...eat it? >>Yes ......? you ate the cake then notice a letter ...read it? >>Yes ''dear souji we're still mad at you for signing us up for the beauty pagent so enjoy! from -chie and yukiko'' ...you start to feel dizzy...memories of the school campout came back...you seriously regret that!...........note to self: stop eating stuff from dojima's fridge....you remember your﻿ mad at yosuke...................give him the cake? >>Yes MWAHAHAHA!
TheRainbowkelly 





You open the fridge.
There's a﻿ good-looking Spoiler inside.
...Eat it?
>>Yes.
>No.
...
Your Courage has increased.
Your Knowledge has increased.
Your Mood has decreased.
Yoomero8D



 >You opened the Fridge >Inside it a bowl filled with purple substance >....eat it? >>>Yes >No ......... .................. >It was Mystery food X! >All your﻿ stats have been reduced to 0, all your social links have reversed, you've got a weird itch, someone stole your wallet, and Margret emptied out the compendium. >You decided screw it your going home GAME OVER
Cloud33






You opened the fridge...
You found Rise drunk in there.
Take her to bed...
>>Yes.
>No.
After you put Rise in bed, she grabs your hand and she tells you﻿ to sleep with her.
Stay for a while?
>>Hell yes.
>...Err...no.
falcolegend




 You opened the fridge... You found Nanako inside. It seems she wants to marry you. Accept her purposal? >>Yes >No Ryotaro rushed in Ryotaro: WHAT﻿ THE HELL ARE YOU DOING!!!! You were arrested for pedophilia All your social links have gone to full negative. Whole Inaba hates you
Deadagent 






You Opened the fridge...
There's some fortune cookies inside.
...Take one?
>>Yes
>no
You ate the fortune cookies.
You read the fortune...
... It says...
YOU LOST﻿ THE GAME
Skinnydevil1995 



 >You come into the living room and notice a small record player next to Dojima. Odd. >You open the fridge. >There seems to be a newspaper inside. >You ask Dojima-san about it. Dojima: Hm? There was a paper in the fridge? Let me see it. >You grab the paper and hand it to Dojima-san. Dojima: Strange, I thought this paper would carry a certain ornithological piece. A story of an...avian variety. I mean,﻿ haven't you heard? >How strange...Ask him what he means? >>Yes >No Nanako: NO BIG BRO DON'T!
Voxerik 






>You open the fridge
>You see a model rocket
>There's note attached: To Russia
> Eat It?
>>Yes
>No
>Dee Dee Ramone comes back as a shadow and asks if﻿ you've heard about the word.
LeoJohnGalt






You opened the fridge.

You see the videogame "Persona 4" inside.

...Play it?

>>Yes

No

....

You don't know why, but you feel like you've been controled by yourself...

You decide﻿ to head straight to bed.

Agusloquillo






>you﻿ opened the fridge.

>you see a copy of the surfing bird cd. will you play it?

>yes

no

*nanako points gun in her mouth*

>1 week later.....

MC- Nanako, havent you heard!?

Nanako- about what?

Dojima- nanako, wait---!

MC- BIRD IS THE WORD!

swordfish1390 






>You opened the fridge.

>You see﻿ a "Mara" figurine.

>...Upon closer inspection, Mara's figurine turns out to be flexible... like those women's equipments.

>...

>You decided to leave it inside.
